S. Guy Endore papers, 1925-1970
UCLA Library Special Collections
S. Guy Endore papers,
1925-1970
279
Endore, S. Guy, 1901-1970
93 boxes (46.5 linear ft.)
S. Guy Endore (1901-70) was a prolific author of books as well as television and movie scripts. His script, G.I. Joe, was nominated for an Oscar in 1945. He was reputedly blacklisted by the Hollywood studios for his political views in the late 1940s. Endore devoted much of his time to the Synanon Foundation after being blacklisted. The collection consists of Endore's manuscripts and typescripts for plays, novels, and television shows. Other materials include clippings and printed materials, many of which address and review Endore's writings. The collection also contains materials related to the House Un-American Activities Committee and the Hollywood Blacklist, the Sleepy Lagoon Defense Committee, the assassination of President Kennedy, and the Warren Commission Report. Books from Endore's library and correspondence (including fan mail) are also included. The finding aid contains an extensive name index.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF. Advance notice is required for access to the collection. Please contact UCLA Library Special Collections for paging information.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of S. Guy Endore, 1956-68.
Gift of Henrietta Endore, 1972.
Gift of Gita Endore, 1972-87.
Gift of Marcia Endore Goodman, 1990.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 1217978
Biography
S. Guy Endore was born in 1901; author of 15 books, including King of Paris, Casanova--His Known and Unknown Life, Voltaire! Voltaire!, and Man from Limbo; wrote screenplays, including Captain Sinbad, Johnny Allegro, Song of Russia, He Ran All the Way, Werewolf of Paris, Methinks the Lady, and Devil Doll; his script, G.I. Joe, was nominated for an Oscar, 1945; was reputedly blacklisted by the studios for his political views, late 1940s; devoted much of his time to the Synanon Foundation; died February 12, 1970.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of Endore's manuscripts and typescripts for plays, novels, and television shows. Other materials include clippings and printed materials, many of which address and review Endore's writings. Collection also contains materials related to the House Un-American Activities Committee and the Hollywood Blacklist, the Sleepy Lagoon Defense Committee, the assassination of President Kennedy, and the Warren Commission Report. Books from Endore's library and correspondence (including fan mail) are also included. Finding aid contains an extensive name index.
Portions of this collection are in French, German and Spanish.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged by subject and titles.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Endore, S. Guy, 1901-1970--Archives.; Sleepy Lagoon Defense Committee (Los Angeles, Calif.); United States--Warren Commission--Report of the President's Commission on the Assassination of President John F. Kennedy.; United States--Congress--House--Committee on Un-American Activities.; Authors, American--California--Los Angeles--Archival resources.; Screenwriters--California--Los Angeles.; Blacklisting of authors--California--Los Angeles.
Items Removed from Collection
The contents of Box 25 have been transferred to UCLA University Archives, Record Series 507, Box 26. The material is restricted -- “No quotation, publication or reproduction without written permission of legal heir.”
Related Oral History
The following oral history is available through the UCLA Library Center for Oral History Research:
Reflections of Guy Endore (oral history transcript) / S. Guy Endore, interviewee. UCLA Oral History Department interview, 1961-62. Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
Container List
- Papers
  - Photograph of Guy Endore., July 3, 1946 (mailed) (Box 1)
  - Correspondence., 1958-1959; (3 items) (Box 1)
  - Doodles and ephemera re Guy Endore., (5 items) (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous notes by Guy Endore., (8 items, holograph) (Box 29)
  - Endore, Guy. Talk to Dr. Powell's class in the Library School, Los Angeles. Thursday morning., December 15, 1960; (9 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections in red ink and pencil) (Box 18)
  - Endore, Guy. Interview. Los Angeles., 1961-1962; (5 reels [7 in.] 3.75 in. per sec. Tape. 11 hours on two tracks); This tape was made by Mrs. Elizabeth I. Dixon under the auspices of the Oral History Program, University of California, Los Angeles. (Box 25)
    The contents of Box 25 have been transferred to UCLA University Archives, Record Series 507, Box 26. The material is restricted -- “No quotation, publication or reproduction without written permission of legal heir.”
  - -- ----. (Unedited tapescript). Los Angeles., 1962; (306 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 25)
    (For the final edited version, see Collection 300: California, University, Los Angeles. Oral History Program)
  - Daily journal(?). n.p., 1949-1952; (15 leaves, typescript) (Box 41)
  - Notes. English 131. Professor Nevius. UCLA(?) Los Angeles., undated; (18 leaves Holograph. Pages have been torn from a notebook) (Box 45)
  - Guy Endore, doodler. n.p., undated; (3 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 48)
    Addition, May 1986
  - Endore, Guy. Typescript with holograph corrections in red ink., Friday, May 25, 1962; (20 leaves, 36 cm.) (Box 21)
    From a talk given by the author before the graduating class of the School of Library Service, University of California, Los Angeles.
    Inscribed, “For Lawrence Clark Powell, chairman of the department of Library Service, UCLA. Dear Larry, here it is. October 15, 1962.”
  - Manuscripts, Fleishman correspondence, Fan mail, etc. (Box 99)
    Addition, June 5, 1990
- Manuscripts by Guy Endore
  - Autobiographical Materials., 1949-1955 and undated (Boxes 11, 39, 93, 95, 96, 98)
    - Notes., July 24, 1949-June 1955; (Typescript with holograph corrections, iregular pagination. 17 reels microfilm) (Box 11)
    - Autobiography(?). n.p., undated; (pp.2-68, typescript carbon) (Box 39)
    - Untitled manuscript - autobiography[?]. n.p., undated; (217pp., typescript carbon with holograph corrections) (Box 93)
      re Sammy Gordon.
    - Untitled manuscript - autobiography[?]. n.p., undated; (200 leaves, Holograph and typescript) (Box 93)
      Manuscript pages.
    - Endore's autobiography., (6 reels microfilm) (Box 95)
    - Autobiography and unidentified., (6 reels microfilm) (Box 96)
    - Autobiography., (5 reels microfilm) (Box 98)
  - As I remember and later knew Isador Goldstein. n.p., undated; (8 leaves, typescript) (Box 39)
  - Babouk. n.p., undated (Boxes 39, 67)
    See also Box 97.
    - Typescript carbon., undated; (204 leaves) (Box 39)
    - Stage adaptation by Lester Fuller. n.p., undated; (138 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 39)
    - Ephemera., (106 items) (Box 67)
      Included are newsclippings, advertisements, publications, reviews, and other material.
  - Background of a forthcoming novel. n.p., undated; (9 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 39)
    With Endore's note, Lecture University of Southern California Librarians on Sade novel.
  - Background of a forthcoming novel. n.p., undated; (8 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 39)
    Also, a variant copy with holograph corrections (8 leaves, typescript).
  - Background of a forthcoming novel. n.p., undated; (21 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 39)
  - Battle of the Philosophers., (Typescript and mimeographed with corrections. 1 reel, negative) (Box 11)
    See also Box 97
  - The Beauty of a One-Dollar Bill. Los Angeles., 1969 (Box 39)
    - Reproduction of typescript., (37 leaves) (Box 39)
      With another copy and letter of transmittal, George Willner to Guy Endore, Los Angeles, August 13, 1969.
    - Typescript with holograph corrections., (14 leaves) (Box 39)
      Also, variant copy (Reproduction) with holograph corrections (14 leaves).
  - The Best of Dumas. Los Angeles., 1961-1962 (Boxes 20, 22, 54, 67)
    Also, related materials.
    [Published, New York: Doubleday, Spring 1962]
    - Typescript with copious corrections on paper., 1961; (583 leaves, 35 cm. in length and 27.5 cm. in width) (Box 20)
    - Typescript from which type was set. n.p., 1961; (599 leaves, typescript with corrections, some holograph) (Box 22)
    - Galley proofs., 1962; (152 sheets) (Box 22)
    - Page proofs., 1962; (469pp.) (Box 22)
    - Dumas and the Romantic Era. n.p., undated; (9pp., typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 54)
      Endore's notes for scenes and musical numbers.
    - Photographs and negatives., (4 items) (Box 54)
      1 photo of Dumas's tomb, 2 negatives of his birthplace, 1 negative of Dumas with a parrot
    - Notes for screenplay/staging. n.p., undated; (15 leaves, holograph and typescript) (Box 54)
    - Dumas and son! A romantic musical. Book by Jerome Chodorov, Music and lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest. Los Angeles., 1967; (137pp., mimeograph. With blue cover) (Box 54)
      Pre-rehearsal script for the 1967 season of the Los Angeles and San Francisco Civic Light Opera Associations.
    - Dumas & Son suit. v.p., 1967-1968; (50 leaves Holograph, typescript, typescript (carbon), reproduction of typescript) (Box 54)
      Includes correspondence, notes, documents, and ephemera regarding Endore's suit against the Los Angeles Civic Light Opera Association for copyright infringement.
    - Ephemera., (44 items) (Box 67)
      An autobiography and anthology.
  - The Big Jump. Final draft screenplay. Los Angeles., November 3, 1948; (117 leaves) (Box 39)
    With revisions dated November 19 and 22. Production no.1187, Columbia Pictures Corporation.
    Also known as: Johnny Allegro(?)
  - Black Magic. n.p., undated; (15 leaves, typescript with a blue cover) (Box 39)
    With another copy (15 leaves, typescript carbon).
  - Black and White and The Clipper. n.p., November 23, 1967 (Box 39)
    - Introduction with holograph corrections., (4 leaves, typescript) (Box 39)
    - Introduction., (6 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 39)
      With 2 additional pages.
  - The Burning Bush. Hollywood and n.p., July-September 1947 (Box 40)
    - Typescript carbon with holograph corrections in pencil. n.p., July-August 1947; (137pp., with a blue cover with doodling on the label) (Box 40)
    - Mimeograph with holograph corrections. Hollywood., September 19, 1947; (pp.26-96. With faded grey/tan cover) (Box 40)
      William Wilder, 5746 Sunset Boulevard, Hollywood 28, California, HO 5358 on the cover.
    - Mimeograph with holograph corrections. Hollywood., September 19, 1947; (96pp.) (Box 40)
      With holograph notes and additional pages of dialogue laid in. With William Wilder's address and phone number on the title page
  - The Business of Writing. n.p., undated; (13 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 40)
  - Call me Shakespeare. A Play of Sorts. Los Angeles., 1966 (Boxes 28-29, 64-65)
    - Typescript with numerous holograph corrections., 1966; (400 leaves) (Box 28)
    - 3 different versions. Los Angeles., 1966; (Mimeographed, 1 copy) (Box 29)
      With holograph corrections.
    - Correspondence. v.p., 1965-1969; (100 items) (Box 64)
      Regarding attempts to produce the play with 2 clippings.
    - Mimeograph. n.p., undated; (57pp., with yellow cover) (Box 64)
      This version includes production note.
      With 3 additional copies.
    - Mimeograph. n.p., undated; (57pp., with blue covers) (Box 64)
      6 copies.
    - Mimeograph. n.p., undated; (74pp., with light green cover) (Box 65)
      With 2 additional copies.
    - Mimeograph. n.p., undated; (74pp., with blue cover) (Box 65)
  - A Christmas Story. n.p., undated; (5 leaves, typescript) (Box 40)
  - Colossal. n.p., undated; (51 leaves, typescript carbon with an orange cover) (Box 40)
  - Conscience of a Writer. n.p., undated; (4 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 40)
    With a variant copy (4 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections).
  - Corvey Dallard. n.p., undated; (16 leaves - 14 numbered pages, typescript carbon) (Box 40)
  - The Coward. New York., undated; (4 leaves, typescript) (Box 40)
  - The Crime at Scottsboro. Hollywood: Hollywood Scottsboro Committee., undated; (40 leaves, booklet) (Box 29)
  - The Dangerous Heart. n.p., undated; (43 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 41)
  - Detour at Midnight. New York: Simon & Schuster., 1959 (Boxes 1-2, 11, 17, 41, 67)
    Variant titles: Detour, Detour at Night, Detour Through Devon and Detour at Devon
    [See also, Box 97 microfilm]
    - “Original version” entitled Detour., 1959; (Mimeographed copy) (Box 1)
    - Detour at Night. New York: Simon & Schuster., 1959 (Boxes 1, 17, 67)
      - 1959 (Box 1)
      - Printer's copy for the American edition., 1959; (187 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 17)
      - Ephemera - German reviews., (13 items) (Box 67)
      - Ephemera., (39 items) (Box 67)
    - Umweg bei Neicht (German version). Stuttgart: J.G. Cotta., 1959 (Box 1)
    - Detour Through Devon, by Hugh King (pseudonym) (Boxes 1, 2, 11, 41)
      Published as Detour at Night, etc.
      - Mimeographed copy (Box 1)
      - Typescript and mimeographed with holograph corrections (Box 2)
      - Typescript and mimeographed with corrections., (1 reel, negative microfilm) (Box 11)
      - Typescript and mimeograph. n.p., undated; (pp.3-99, with partial red cover) (Box 41)
      - Miscellaneous pages. n.p., undated; (2 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 41)
  - The Devil and Mark Twain. n.p., undated (Boxes 2, 41)
    - Typescript., (Irregular pagination) (Box 2)
      Also: another copy (Typescript carbon with holograph corrections).
    - Typescript., (44 leaves) (Box 41)
  - Diamonds. n.p., 1965; (21 leaves, holograph with typescript notes) (Box 41)
    With prose poem, A capsule history of Diamonds (16 leaves, Typescript carbon).
    Also, letter to John Robertson, Holiday Magazine, and clipping
  - Dostoevsky. n.p., undated; (40 leaves, typescript and holograph notes) (Box 41)
  - The Dream of a Chrysalis. New York., undated; (8 leaves, typescript) (Box 41)
  - Dreams for Sale. n.p., undated; (51 leaves, typescript carbon with orange cover) (Box 41)
    Submitted by Alex Kemper, Incorporated (Agency).
  - Edgar Allan Poe. Screenplay. n.p., undated; (99pp., typescript carbon with orange cover) (Box 41)
    With chronology, notes, and foreword.
  - Entomophagy. n.p., undated; (60 leaves, typescript and holograph) (Box 41)
    Includes 1 notebook and drafts of article.
  - An Evening in the Theatre with Jewish Literature. Los Angeles., 1965 (Box 41)
    - Mimeograph., (7 leaves) (Box 41)
    - University of Judaism production., (33 leaves, variously numbered, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 41)
      With another copy.
  - False Witness (Boxes 11, 28, 49)
    - Typescript and mimeographed with corrections., (1 reel, negative microfilm) (Box 11)
    - Transcript with many holograph corrections. n.p., undated; (43 leaves, photocopy) (Box 28)
    - Correspondence re False Witness. Los Angeles., 1952-1954; (4 items) (Box 49)
      Includes carbons of letters to Carey McWilliams, Elinor Kirstein, and draft of an open letter to Whittaker Chambers with a copy of the Saturday Review, May 24, 1952.
    - Draft pages and notes. n.p., undated; (9 leaves (Box 49)
    - False Witness. By Elinor Kirstein. n.p., undated; (148pp., typescript carbon) (Box 49)
    - Typescript carbon. n.p., undated; (148pp.) (Box 49)
      Elinor Kirstein's name has been crossed out on the title page
  - French Revolution. n.p., undated; (8 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 41)
  - The Future. n.p., undated; (18 leaves, typescript) (Box 41)
  - The Gamblers., 1942 and undated (Box 42)
    - First draft continuity by Guy Endore, and note that this was done for Warner Brothers., (167pp., typescript with holograph corrections, with blue cover) (Box 42)
    - Typescript carbon. n.p., July 11, 1942; (99pp., with blue cover) (Box 42)
  - Gettysburg. Los Angeles and n.p., 1966 and undated (Box 42)
    - Step outline for wedding at Gettysburg. n.p., May 24, 1966; (4 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 42)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections. n.p., undated; (24pp.) (Box 42)
    - Typescript with holograph notes. n.p., undated; (21 leaves, various pages) (Box 42)
    - Reproduction of typescript. n.p., undated; (15 leaves) (Box 42)
    - Typescript carbon. Los Angeles., undated; (43pp., with red cover) (Box 42)
      Also, another copy with tan cover.
  - The Giant Brain. n.p., undated; (17 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections. Pages are variously numbered 4 through 29) (Box 42)
    With Endore's note, “formerly Computer Story.”
  - Gold Lotus. A Chinese novel. Far Rockaway, Long Island., undated; (10pp., typescript) (Box 42)
    Synopsis for screen treatment(?).
  - The Golden Nail. A novel about Victor Hugo. n.p., undated (Boxes 50-51)
    Also known as: The Master
    - Typescript., (37pp.) (Box 50)
    - Reproduction of typescript., (12pp.) (Box 50)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections., (pp.4-33) (Box 50)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections., (24pp. Typescript) (Box 50)
    - Chronology of Victor Hugo's life., (37 leaves, photocopy) (Box 50)
      With annotations by Guy Endore. Source unidentified.
    - Notes re Victor Hugo., (7 leaves, holograph and typescript) (Box 50)
    - Books about Victor Hugo., (8 items) (Box 50)
    - Working drafts of various chapters of Hugo's life, arranged in small groups by Endore., (Holograph, typescript, and typescript carbon) (Box 51)
      6 folders: folders 1-5, 150 leaves each, folder 6, 50 leaves
  - The Gordons. n.p., undated; (8 leaves [9pp.], typescript carbon with holograph corrections) (Box 42)
  - G.I. Joe, a screenplay (Boxes 28, 42, 68)
    - Group of ephemera relating to G.I. Joe., (21 items) (Box 28)
    - First draft. Screenplay by Guy Endore, Phillip Stevenson, Ben Bengal. Hollywood., July 5, 1944; (195pp., mimeograph. Light brown cover) (Box 42)
      With letter from Frank McCarthy, January 7, 1969.
    - Ephemera., (6 items) (Box 68)
  - Le Grand Dictionnaire Universel du XIXeme Siecle. n.p., undated; (5 leaves, holograph) (Box 42)
    With typescript version (3 leaves) and additional pages (3 leaves).
  - Hazing. n.p., undated; (6 leaves Holograph and typescript notes) (Box 42)
    With typescript text from The Sun (August 20, 1899), New York re hazing.
  - He Ran All the Way. Los Angeles., 1950 (Box 42)
    - First draft. Los Angeles., June 1, 1950; (146pp., mimeograph. With grey cover) (Box 42)
      For Roberts Productions, Incorporated, Los Angeles.
    - Typescript carbon with holograph corrections., June 16, 1950; (139pp., with blue cover) (Box 42)
  - Health Food Shoppe. n.p., undated (Boxes 28, 43)
    - Typescript carbon., undated; (23 leaves, bound in folder) (Box 28)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections., undated; (12 leaves) (Box 43)
    - Typescript carbon with holograph corrections., undated; (15 leaves, misnumbered: page 5 omitted, with 2 page 8's) (Box 43)
  - The Heart and the Mind., (Mostly ozalid copies with extensive holograph corrections in pencil and red ink, and some pages of holograph [pages] interspersed) (Boxes 12-17)
    Also, several incomplete typewritten drafts (partly carbon) and one package of holograph notes and notations (box 17).
  - Notes re Heine. n.p., undated; (3 leaves Holograph, Typescript carbon) (Box 43)
  - Hidden Hunger. n.p., 1935; (4pp., typescript carbon) (Box 43)
    - Typescript carbon. n.p., July 15, 1935; (4pp.) (Box 43)
    - Script number 3731, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Script Department. Culver City., July 16, 1935; (47pp., mimeograph) (Box 43)
  - A History of Human Skill. n.p., undated (Box 43)
    - Notes. n.p., undated; (4 leaves, typescript) (Box 43)
    - Introduction to A History of Human Skill. n.p., undated; (12 leaves, typescript (carbon) and holograph) (Box 43)
    - Prospectus. n.p., undated; (73 leaves variously numbered, typescript with partial grey cover) (Box 43)
    - Portions of text. Los Angeles., 1942; (150 leaves, typescript and typescript carbon) (Box 43)
      With letter of transmittal to Angus Cameron, Little, Brown & Company, May 9, 1942.
  - Hollywood Anti-Nazi League Program. (Hollywood)., December 8, 1937; (6 leaves, typescript carbon) (Box 43)
    Text for a radio broadcast.
  - How the Alligator Was Cured of Heart-Trouble. New York., July 23, 1933; (32pp., typescript) (Box 43)
  - How to Become a Human Being. n.p., undated; (20 leaves, typescript and holograph) (Box 43)
  - I Came Back. As recorded by Guy Endore from conversations with 1st. Lieutenant Hugh Enfield of the U.S. Marine Corps. n.p., undated (Boxes 29, 44)
    - Typescript., undated; (173 leaves, in black cover) (Box 29)
    - Typescript carbon., undated; (173pp.) (Box 44)
    - Typescript carbon., undated; (173pp., with black cover) (Box 44)
      With newsclipping re B.P. Schulberg.
  - I Don't Believe in Ghosts. By Hugh King (pseudonym?). n.p., undated; (6 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 44)
    With another version.
  - Idle Hands. New York., undated; (8 leaves, typescript) (Box 44)
  - Jacob Fugger the Rich. The birth of capitalism. n.p., undated; (24pp., typescript) (Box 44)
  - Jews and history. Hollywood., 1965; (37pp., mimeograph) (Box 44)
    - University of Judaism production., (37pp., mimeograph) (Box 44)
    - Typescript carbon and mimeograph with holograph corrections. n.p., undated; (38pp.) (Box 44)
    - Typescript and mimeograph., 1965; (37pp.) (Box 44)
  - Justice for Salcido. Los Angeles: Civil Rights Council., 1948; (Mimeographed copy, inscribed. In brown paper cover) (Box 1)
  - Karl Freund. n.p., undated; (2 leaves, typescript with holograph corrections) (Box 44)
    With photocopy.
  - Khyber Pass (Copy no.5). A story treatment by Guy Endore. King Brothers Productions, Incorporated, Hollywood., undated; (24pp., typescript carbon with dark blue cover) (Box 44)
  - The King of Monte-Cristo. Hollywood., undated; (15pp., typescript with grey cover, red label) (Box 44)
    With another copy, from George Landy.
  - King of Paris. New York: Simon & Schuster., 1966 (Boxes 2-8, 20, 44, 52-54, 67)
    - Proof copy. (Box 2)
      Includes typescript copy of epilogue and printed advertisements.
    - Typescript. (Box 3)
      Also: color photograph of Gerome's Duel After the Masquerade Ball.
    - Typescript and holograph with corrections., (Irregular pagination) (Boxes 4-7)
    - Typescript carbon (Box 8)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections re King of Paris. n.p., undated; (1 leaf) (Box 44)
    - Screenplay by Robert I. Holt. Based on the novel by Guy Endore. Beverly Hills., undated; (190pp., mimeograph. With blue cover) (Box 52)
      Seven Arts Associated Corps. Producer: Stanley Rubin.
    - Screenplay by Guy Endore for Seven Arts Productions. Los Angeles., undated; (321 leaves, mimeographed. In a grey manila folder) (Boxes 20, 52-53)
      - Mimeographed., undated; (321 leaves. In a grey manila folder) (Box 20)
      - With note that this is second carbon., undated; (185pp., typescript carbon. Lacking p.184) (Box 52)
      - With Endore's note, “volume one”., undated; (pp.1-160. Typescript carbon) (Box 52)
      - With Endore's note, “volume two”., (pp.161-321. Typescript carbon) (Box 52)
      - With Endore's note that this is (short version). volume three., undated; (185pp., typescript carbon) (Box 52)
      - Typescript carbon., undated; (320pp. With blue cover) (Box 52)
      - Mimeograph., undated; (321pp. With beige cover) (Box 53)